Contact

9087825116 (Mobile) kamal.dev9339@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kamal-dev (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Information Security
Penetration Testing
Ethical Hacking

Languages

Hindi English

Certifications

Certificate of Continuing Education Completion

Training and Internship Certificate on Ethical Hacking

Startup India Learning Program
Web App Security Fundamentals

Kamal Dev

Co-Founder at Alpyus Technologies Bengaluru

Summary

Technology and Business has always been a driving factor for my personal and intellectual growth. I am from a computer science background but keenly interested into business, this has led to a special bond in my brain that makes me link every technical opportunity to a business opportunity.

I have worked as a Software Engineer Intern at Intel at high end technologies with genius minds towards a new innovative tech driven future. Challenges are something that makes me go crazy. And at Intel, my each and every day used to be filled with challenges to meet up with industry standard and always keep on learning new things to be updated with technology.

I have been an entrepreneur since very childhood. I used to sell inks in school for small pennies as in our school we were only allowed to use ink pens and not the ball pens. Also in my school days I have been involved in lending out my bicycles to other fellow students who didn't had a bicycle at that time. These were some small activities how I started my interest in business. Now speaking of my actual, legal previous experience, in my class 12th, I founded Follery Pvt Ltd, an E-commerce company that was dealing with Fine Art products. To some extent this was going well but I faced problems in scaling this up. This was my successful failure experience where I learned two things - Importance of Market Understanding and Importance of a strong Team. After this I also worked on two more business one in Healthcare sector and another in Digital Magazine but both ended up to be a good learning and experience for me.

Health, Education, Sanitation and Latest Techs, these are the major domains of my interest and most of my work has always been in these sectors. My capability to grasp things fast and to work till perfection makes me capable of taking up any kind of work and excelling in that. I am always up for any kind of collaboration and projects in any of the above mentioned domain.

Experience

Alpyus Technologies Co-Founder July 2020 - Present (2 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Intel Corporation
Software Engineer Intern
July 2019 - June 2020 (1 year)
Bengaluru Area, India

Japan Third Party Humanoid Developer Intern March 2019 - April 2019 (2 months)

Follery Pvt. Ltd.
CEO and Director
December 2016 - September 2018 (1 year 10 months)
India

AICRA-All India Council for Robotics & Automation Internship Trainee May 2018 - June 2018 (2 months) Worked in Cyber Security and Penetration Testing

Education

Vellore Institute of Technology
Master of Technology (MTech) Integrated, Software
Engineering · (2015 - 2020)

Kairali School Secondary High School · (2013 - 2015)

St. Francis School, Ranchi High School · (2005 - 2013)